Angela Hall

Chandler, AZ 85225 (480) 278-5022 angelarhall@gmail.com LinkedIn/Angelarhall-phx

Systems and Software engineer with close to 9 years of knowledge in various industries. Knowledgeable about both operations and engineering practices with the ability to implement best processes for users.

EXPERIENCE

Strongmind, Chandler, AZ—DevOps II/Software Engineer Dec 2019 - September 2020

- Set up and administer services through AWS. (API Gateway, S3 buckets, Lambda, EC2 servers, and DynamoDBs)
- Spearheaded set up and centralization of alerts using logging and metric tracking tools (**CloudWatch**, **Graphana**, and **PowerBI**)
- Create database queries to accurately update student information for state reporting (MSSQL, Snowflake, C#)

Carvana, Tempe, AZ— *Support/Software Engineer* September 2017 to October 2019

- Led push to utilize project and issue tracking software to effectively communicate team priorities to stakeholders. (Jira, Confluence, and Tableau)
- Coordinated project management practices to track deployments and commitments. (Agile)
- Programmed the sites widely used APIs using Microsoft Stack. (Azure Devops, C# .NET, and Asynchronous architecture)
- Launched responsive front end pages. (React, Angular, JQuery, HTML5, and CSS)

Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ — *Data/Database Analyst* September 2016 to April 2017

- Developed and deployed SSIS Packages (**SQL Server**)
- Administered and built CRM administration tools and services. (Salesforce)
- Prepared business specifications to request bug fixes, enhancements, and new features. (SCRUM)

Pearson Education, Chandler, AZ—*PowerSchool Technical Support Specialist* September 2011 to January 2015

- Diagnosed hardware and software issues for all operating systems, web-based services, errors and other content issues. (**Powerschool**, and other **Pearson** based products)
- Trained staff and teachers about the student data administration processes. (**Training**)
- Decreased customer call backs and coached other members of the team on effective troubleshooting procedures. (Metrics and Peer Coaching)

EDUCATION

ITT Technical Institute — Associate of Applied Science in Information Systems Administration